Legends aren't born that way
传奇并非天成
But by deeds
但由功迹铸就
Bloodlines denotes nothing
所谓血脉 无足轻重
How do towering trees grow from a seed?
巨木何以擢于微种？
And achievements rise from the ash?
丰碑何以立于余烬？
We endure and suffer lose and bleed
历经失却 饮痛沥血
Still we clash against the sky
天穹尚晦仍应相搏
You and I are weak like the reeds
纵使此身脆弱只如苇草
But chasing flames is carved into creed, Ohh
然为逐火焚身已成信条
Cleave the darkness, seize the light
辟夜求光
Daybreak's meant to be free
斫断镣铐
We are gonna shatter the ties
所谓破晓生来自由
Time's worn away the lives
岁月磨蚀生命
And bygones
往事亦如烟消
Leaving faith to resound
唯有信仰 流传回荡
Behold all the pioneering souls
凝神回望先辈英魄
In the gloom, they strive to flash
昏晦之中竭力闪灼
Though the journey’s filled with wounds and tolls
鳞伤遍体 牺牲塞途
Still we clash against the sky
天穹尚晦 仍应相搏
Let's defy the judgment of flaws
纵使缺瑕伴身 绝不卑屈
Would rather die than kneel down or crawl, Ohh
宁为逐火焚身 亦不跪降
Cleave the darkness, seize the light
辟夜求光
Daybreak's meant to be free
斫断镣铐
We are gonna shatter the ties
所谓破晓 生来自由
You and I, Still gonna against the sky
你我仍将與天穹相搏
You and I, And we are gonna face the fight
你我将为崛起而生，破晓而行
You and I, Still gonna against the sky
你我仍将與天穹相搏
You and I, And we are gonna face the fight
你我将为崛起而生，破晓而行
You and I, Still gonna against the sky
你我仍将與天穹相搏
You and I, And we are gonna face the fight
你我将为崛起而生，破晓而行
You and I, Still gonna against the sky
你我仍将與天穹相搏
Oh-ooh
You and I are weak like the reeds
纵使此身脆弱 只如苇草
Aah
But chasing flames is carved into creed
然为逐火焚身 已成信条
Ooh
Cleave the darkness, seize the light
辟夜求光
A brand new dawn’s within reach
咫尺侵晨
We are gonna make it untied
所谓破晓 终将自由